<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache Software Foundation Events</title>
    <link>https://events.apache.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Apache Software Foundation Events</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://events.apache.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Apache Roadshows</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/about/roadshow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/about/roadshow.html</guid>
      <description>Apache Roadshows are small regional one- or two-day events, intended to build local community and educate about what the Apache Software Foundation does.
While not a traditional roadshow (ie, a traveling event with multiple stops), we use the name to indicate that there may be multiple small events on a particular continent. Thus, the Europe Roadshow may have small events in Berlin and Barcelona during the course of a year, while the North America Roadshow might have events in DC and Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About ASF Events</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) runs, or participates in some fashion in, a number of different types of events, which different target audiences and goals, to educate about our projects and about the Foundation, and to build the communities.
The main types of event we work with around ASF projects are:
Community Over Code - the ASF&amp;rsquo;s official conference Roadshows - bringing ASF content around the world Endorsed events - run by third parties using Apache brands If you want to organize your own event that uses ASF brands or trademarks in any way, we strongly encourage you to coordinate with us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Community Over Code</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/about/commcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/about/commcode/</guid>
      <description>Community Over Code (formerly ApacheCon) is the official conference of the Apache Software Foundation. Its primary goals are education and community building. We try to produce one each calendar year somewhere in North America and Europe, and are working on expanding this to the rest of the world.
If you want to volunteer to help with Community Over Code, please join our mailing lists, and see what volunteer opportunities we have, bearing in mind that it sometimes gets out of date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Conferences and Events Mailing Lists</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/involved/mailing-lists.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/involved/mailing-lists.html</guid>
      <description>There are several main mailing lists on which discussion and planning of Apache Software Foundation events occurs:
ApacheCon Announce announce@apachecon.com Subscription address: announce-subscribe@apachecon.com Archives: Web archives Use: Read-only: Announcements of, and details about, Apache events ApacheCon Discuss apachecon-discuss@apache.org Subscription address: apachecon-discuss-subscribe@apache.org Archives: Web archives Use: Public discussion of Apache events Community Development dev@community.apache.org Subscription address: dev-subscribe@community.apache.org Archives: Web archives Use: Since events are produced and organized by the Apache community development PMC, most event discussion starts on the ComDev mailing list Planners (Planning committee members only) planners@apachecon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Conferences Calendar</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/event/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Apache events This is the list of upcoming official Apache events, and those events which have been approved to use Apache Marks under the Third Party Event Branding Policy.
Sorry, this requires Javascript For a complete list of events see our calendar.
In addition to Official Apache Events, there are a wide range of other events which feature Apache projects and technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Conferences Calendar</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/event/calendar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/event/calendar.html</guid>
      <description>This Calendar is maintained by the Apache Conferences Committee (ConCom). It&amp;rsquo;s used to list official Apache events, and those events which have been approved to use Apache Marks under the Third Party Event Branding Policy.
The calendar can be viewed at https://www.google.com/calendar/&amp;hellip;
This Calendar is also available as an iCal feed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Endorsed Events</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/about/endorsed.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/about/endorsed.html</guid>
      <description>Apache endorsed/approved events There are many third-party events produced every year that focus on Apache Software Foundation projects. The ASF encourages these events, as they expand the reach of our projects and our message.
If you are producing an Apache-related event, and using our brands and marks, we ask that contact us for our official approval. Along with this, we will also help promote these events, where possible and appropriate. Whether or not you want to collaborate with us on your event, you MUST adhere to our branding policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Event Logos</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/organize/logos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/organize/logos/</guid>
      <description>The use of Apache Logos and Marks is controlled. For information on using Apache Logos and Marks in general, please see the Apache Trademark Policy. For information on using Apache Logos and Marks for external events, please see the Third Party Event Branding Policy.
For events that have been approved to use Apache Logos (typically events being organized by Apache committers and projects, which have been approved by ConCom), a number of Event Logos are available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Past Events</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/event/past-events.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/event/past-events.html</guid>
      <description>Past ApacheCons For details on past ApacheCons, and archived sites of previous events (where available), please see https://archive.apachecon.com/
Information on past ApacheCons is also available on the ApacheCon Wiki</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ApacheCon Events</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/x/current-event.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/x/current-event.html</guid>
      <description>ApacheCon ApacheCon is the place to come to learn what Apache projects are doing, as well as a place for projects to come to build stronger project communities, as well as forge the bonds between projects. For more information about ApacheCon, please go to ApacheCon.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ApacheCon playbook</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/about/commcode/playbook.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/about/commcode/playbook.html</guid>
      <description>This playbook is focused at ApacheCon or Roadshow volunteers who are actively involved in planning and running Apache events. Please be sure to bring your questions to the planners@ mailing list!
What to do before, during, and after an Apache event This is a set of recommended actions that an event organizer may do before, during, and after ApacheCon.
Many of the recommendations in here can, of course, be applied to any Apache event or Roadshow, including third-party events, or project events run by PMCs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Involved in Apache Events</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/involved/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of different ways to get involved with Events at Apache. Many of these come under the umbrella of the Conferences Committee, but some fall under different groups, such as the Apache Community Development Project.
If you are an Apache Committer, and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in putting on an Apache Event, please see the Organising Events section for more help. If you are interested in helping others out with putting on an Apache Event, you are advised to join the appropriate mailing list, and volunteer for events there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize an Apache Event</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/organize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/organize/</guid>
      <description>If you want to host your own Apache project event, or propose a roadshow about the ASF, get in touch with us on the Event Planning mailing list.
Important! While we appreciate other parties producing events to tell the world about our many great Apache projects and communities, Apache trademarks and brands are also important to us. To use any Apache trademarks in conjunctions with events, you must request permission by following the Third Party Event Branding Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadshow Bid Process</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/organize/roadshow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/organize/roadshow.html</guid>
      <description>DRAFT This is intended to document the bid process for running/hosting a Roadshow. In particular, if you want ASF budget for it.
You need, at a minimum
Event chair Must be an ASF member Must be resident in the city where the event is proposed Volunteers to support (how many?) City/Venue selected University cities are preferred Local tech firms that can sponsor? Local keynote suggestion Proposed timeline, starting with CFP, going through schedule, speaker notification, the event, and the post-event Budget Leads on sponsorship helpful Contribute to event &amp;ldquo;runbook&amp;rdquo; as output from the event To run a roadshow or other small event without ASF budget, you only need to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer to help at ApacheCon</title>
      <link>https://events.apache.org/about/commcode/volunteer.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://events.apache.org/about/commcode/volunteer.html</guid>
      <description>Volunteer to help at ApacheCon Coordination of ApacheCon happens on two lists:
The private planners@apachecon.com mailing list for most of the planning work The public apachecon-discuss@apache.org mailing list for general discussion, calls for volunteers, announcements, and so on. At this time, we can use help in the following areas - typically for each ApacheCon that happens. To volunteer, please send email to the apachecon-discuss mailing list indicating your availability.
Calls For Papers The CFP for each ApacheCon draws hundreds of submissions about projects all around the ASF.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
